attention towards an exclusive news, our correspondent Arshad
is ready on Saturday evening, he has been appointed to cover news related to the insurance sector,
see, IDEA is making
many changes in insurance and another
big change that is proposed is that the
Finance Solvency Working Group of IRDA has
suggested that there should be a
single limit for the expenses of management, right now what is happening is that there are
different limits for the Joker Commission and the salary and Joga Management expenses, but it has been
proposed by the working group of IDEA
that a single limit should be fixed and if this
single limit is fixed then it will be very positive news for the PSU
companies like New India Assurance
and it will
be very positive news for the private companies because the
expenditure on salaries etc. in private companies is up
to 30 percent, we have said that
in PSU companies
this expenditure is up to 70 percent and so private companies will have a
lot of capital left, so  They will be able to
use that capital in such a way that they will be
able to give more commission, will be
able to give more advertisements and the
market share of PSU will decrease. It has also been
suggested that the fees of PSU companies are
high, salaries are less,
so some concession should be given. Even if that
concession is given, then also the private
company will have a huge room but will have a
huge margin, more commission,
more reports, more advertisements to
expand its business and
increase its market share. Right now the
market share of PSU general insurance companies is 39-40 per cent, so it is a
huge market share, but if this is the
recommendation of the working group, where the
limit of single explanation judge of management is fixed, then it will harm the PSU companies
and private insurance will
benefit a lot. Okay, so private
insurance companies bring good news,
a little negative news for government insurance companies,
if they have the option